Guide to the Coalition to Stop Trident Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Additional Material, 1964-2009; Accession 2015-M-039; 0.02; (1 envelope)
  - Flyers, brochures, newsletters, handouts, postcard, and planning documents of Coalition to Stop Trident and affiliated organizations, 1983-2009 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Newsclippings, 1988-1994 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Protest poetry and song lyrics, 1964-1987 (Box 1, Folder 2)